<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Panos Karabelas</title>
    <link>https://panosk92.github.io/panoskarabelas/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Panos Karabelas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://panosk92.github.io/panoskarabelas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>first blog post</title>
      <link>https://panosk92.github.io/panoskarabelas/posts/first-blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://panosk92.github.io/panoskarabelas/posts/first-blog-post/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://panosk92.github.io/panoskarabelas/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://panosk92.github.io/panoskarabelas/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! My name is Panos, I&amp;rsquo;m the author of Spartan Engine and a Senior Rendering Programmer @ Codemasters.
This site is used both for blogging and as a portfolio.
 Motto
&amp;ldquo;If something is important enough, you do it, even if the odds are not in your favor.&amp;rdquo; Elon Musk
 Games I like
 Alan Wake Assetto Corsa Colin McRae Rally Dirt and Dirt Rally Doom, Dying Light Fallout Far Cry Forza Motorsport Grand Theft Auto Gran Turismo Grim Fandango Hitman Just Cause Kerbal Space Program LA Noire Mass Effect Max Payne Metal Gear Solid Quantum Break Sherlock Holmes Skyrim The Last of Us Uncharted, Wolfenstein  Movies I like</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://panosk92.github.io/panoskarabelas/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://panosk92.github.io/panoskarabelas/projects/</guid>
      <description>Present - Dirt 5  Can&amp;rsquo;t share anything at the moment.
Team: Codemasters • Platform: PC, Stadia, PS4, PS4, Xbox One, Xbox Series X • Tools: C++, Custom • Location: UK
 2017 to 2020 - VR game (cancelled)  I left Greece and moved to the UK to work on an ambitious VR title which after a few years, was cancelled. I worked on my cool things which I am (unfortunately) not allowed to share.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>